hwiweekly.com 2012-05-28

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. This privacy policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website and its affiliates. Any subsequent changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this website. Please review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our practices, as they are subject to change.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. Similarly, we ask that you provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted. You may opt-out at any time and decide not to provide requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will no longer receive the information and/or service you are requesting. We take prudent measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. The information you provide will be used to enable us to contact you regarding new offers, and to improve our site. We also use this information-directly, indirectly, and in combination with data we purchase to introduce you to informational, services, and/or product offerings. When registering and submitting your information on this site, you expressly authorize us and our affiliates to use your personal information, and you expressly agree to receive marketing offers by email, phone, or direct mail. By providing your personal information, you are also consenting to receive newsletters including trusted third party newsletters.

Should you wish to discontinue receiving mailings simply unsubscribe, or you may mail your opt-out request to: Opt-Out, 7558 W. Thunderbird Rd., Suite 1-152, Peoria, AZ 85381. Please be advised that we may automatically collect certain information from visitors to, and members of, this site, such as; Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and click stream data. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. If you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card, we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information may include your name, card number and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you may be using to submit payment if applicable. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of national security, fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose personal information about you to credit agencies, collection agencies, and/or merchant database agencies, as we deem prudent and necessary. You may contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.
